<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="no"?>
<modDesc descVersion="108">
    <author>KryskiPL</author>
    <version>1.0.0.0</version>

    <title>
        <en>Realistic Polish Diesel Price</en>
        <de>Realistischer Polnischer Dieselpreis</de>
        <fr>Prix Réaliste Du Diesel Polonais</fr>
        <pl>Realistyczne Polskie Ceny Diesla</pl>
    </title>

    <description>
<en><![CDATA[A script that changes the global diesel price to an amount close to Polish reality, approximately 6,80 PLN per liter (without the artificial Euro conversion rate). 
Note: the price may fluctuate between 6 PLN and 8 PLN per liter, and buying in a fuel tank is more expensive than at a gas station. 
The modification fully supports multiplayer mode.]]></en>
<de><![CDATA[Ein Skript, das den globalen Dieselpreis an die polnische Realität anpasst, auf etwa 6,80 PLN pro Liter (ohne den künstlichen Euro-Umrechnungskurs). 
Hinweis: Der Preis kann zwischen 6 PLN und 8 PLN pro Liter schwanken, und der Kauf in einem Kraftstofftank ist teurer als an der Tankstelle. 
Die Modifikation unterstützt den Multiplayer-Modus vollständig.]]></de>
<fr><![CDATA[Un script qui modifie le prix global du diesel pour un montant proche de la réalité polonaise, environ 6,80 PLN par litre (sans le taux de conversion artificiel de l'Euro). 
Remarque : le prix peut fluctuer entre 6 PLN et 8 PLN par litre, et l'achat dans une cuve de carburant est plus cher qu'à la station-service. 
La modification prend entièrement en charge le mode multijoueur.]]></fr>
<pl><![CDATA[Skrypt, który zmienia globalną cenę diesla na zbliżoną do polskiej rzeczywistości kwotę około 6,80 zł za litr (bez sztucznego przelicznika z Euro). 
Uwaga: cena może się wahać od 6 zł do 8 zł za litr, a zakup w zbiorniku paliwa jest droższy niż na stacji paliw. 
Modyfikacja w pełni obsługuje tryb multiplayer.]]></pl>
    </description>

    <multiplayer supported="true"/>
    <iconFilename>icon_RealisticPolishDieselPrice.dds</iconFilename>

    <extraSourceFiles>
        <sourceFile filename="RealisticDieselPrice.lua" />
    </extraSourceFiles>

</modDesc>