<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="no"?>
<modDesc descVersion="109">
    <author>KryskiPL</author>
    <version>1.0.0.0</version>

    <title>
        <en>Realistic Polish Diesel Price</en>
        <de>Realistischer Polnischer Dieselpreis</de>
        <fr>Prix Réaliste Du Diesel Polonais</fr>
        <pl>Realistyczne Polskie Ceny Diesla</pl>
    </title>

    <description>
        <en><![CDATA[This script changes the global diesel price to an amount close to Polish reality, setting it to approximately 6.20 Euro per liter (without the conversion rate). 
How to use: The script works automatically in the background after activating the mod. 
There are no hotkeys required. 
Buying fuel from a placeable tank is more expensive than at a public gas station. 
The modification supports multiplayer mode. 
Github: https://github.com/KryskiPL/FS25_RealisticPolishDieselPrice]]></en>
        <de><![CDATA[Dieses Skript ändert den globalen Dieselpreis auf einen Betrag nahe der polnischen Realität und setzt ihn auf etwa 6,20 Euro pro Liter (ohne den Umrechnungskurs). 
Verwendung: Das Skript arbeitet nach der Aktivierung des Mods automatisch im Hintergrund. 
Es werden keine Tastenbelegungen benötigt. 
Der Kauf von Kraftstoff in einem platzierbaren Tank ist teurer als an einer öffentlichen Tankstelle. 
Die Modifikation unterstützt den Multiplayer-Modus. 
Github: https://github.com/KryskiPL/FS25_RealisticPolishDieselPrice]]></de>
        <fr><![CDATA[Ce script modifie le prix global du diesel pour un montant proche de la réalité polonaise, en le fixant à environ 6,20 Euro par litre (sans le taux de conversion). 
Utilisation : Le script fonctionne automatiquement en arrière-plan après l'activation du mod. 
Aucun raccourci clavier n'est requis. 
L'achat de carburant dans une cuve plaçable est plus cher qu'à une station-service publique. 
La modification prend en charge le mode multijoueur. 
Github: https://github.com/KryskiPL/FS25_RealisticPolishDieselPrice]]></fr>
        <pl><![CDATA[Skrypt zmienia globalną cenę diesla na kwotę zbliżoną do polskiej rzeczywistości, ustawiając ją na około 6,20 euro za litr (bez przelicznika).
Jak używać: Skrypt działa automatycznie w tle po aktywacji modyfikacji. 
Mod nie wymaga żadnych skrótów klawiszowych. 
Zakup paliwa w stacjonarnym zbiorniku jest droższy niż na publicznej stacji paliw. 
Modyfikacja obsługuje tryb wieloosobowy. 
Github: https://github.com/KryskiPL/FS25_RealisticPolishDieselPrice]]></pl>
    </description>

    <multiplayer supported="true"/>
    <iconFilename>icon_RealisticPolishDieselPrice.dds</iconFilename>

    <extraSourceFiles>
        <sourceFile filename="RealisticPolishDieselPrice.lua" />
    </extraSourceFiles>

</modDesc>